Imogen Cunningham
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Henry Gallery (University of Washington, Seattle): May 05, 1958; May 15, 1958*; Jul 27, 1960 (2); Aug 03, 1960 (letter from Gryffyd Partridge); Aug 23, 1960*; Mar 26, 1961*; Mar 17, 1964; Mar 19, 1964*; Mar 30, 1964; Apr 16, 1964*; Apr 20, 1964 (2); Apr 24, 1964*; Aug 30, 1964*; Sep 16, 1964; Sep 27, 1964*; Oct 15, 1964; Dec 10, 1964; Dec 30, 1964*; Jan 12, 1965; Jan 18, 1965*; Mar 30, 1965; Mar 31, 1965; Apr 01, 1965*; Apr 21, 1965*; Jun 04, 1965; Jun 17, 1965; Jun 20, 1965; Jun 23, 1965*; Jun 27, 1965*; Jul 20, 1965; Aug 05, 1965*; Nov 10, 1965*; Jan 03, 1966; Jan 14, 1966; Jan 21, 1966*; Jan 24, 1966; Jan 30, 1966*; Feb 11, 1966; Apr 06, 1966; Jun 20, 1966*; Jun 21, 1966; Jul 04, 1966*; Aug 03, 1966; Aug 09, 1966*; Sep 14, 1966; Oct 21, 1966*; Dec 02, 1966; Dec 11, 1966*; Dec 21, 1966; Feb 02, 1967*; Jun 18, 1967*; Oct 31, 1967; Nov 09, 1967*; Sep 15, 1970*; Sep 28, 1970; Nov 07, 1970*; Nov 24, 1970; Jan 16, 1971*; Jan 26, 1971; Feb 24, 1971; Mar 03, 1971*; Apr 26, 1971; Jun 09, 1971; Jun 16, 1971*; May 08, 1972; Jul 11, 1972; Mar 01, 1973; Mar 28, 1973*; Apr 10, 1973; May 07, 1973*; Oct 17, 1973*; Dec 18, 1973; Jan 18, 1974*; Jan 21, 1974; Feb 06, 1974; Feb 07, 1974*; Feb 12, 1974; Feb 20, 1974; Mar 05, 1974*; Mar 20, 1974; Mar 27, 1974*; Mar 28, 1974; Apr 21, 1974; Apr 26, 1974*; May 05, 1974*; May 06, 1974*; May 10, 1974 (including 5 installation photographs from Cunningham's exhibition); Jun 04, 1974
Heron, Edith: Mar 07, 1974
Herrick, Mariam and Francis: Apr 14, 1971; Dec 1973; Dec 26, 1974; May 30, 1975*
Herring, Frances: Apr 15, 1970
Hershey, Ann: see KPIX 5
Heyman, Therese: undated (2); Feb 26, 1965*; Dec 20, 1965; Apr 25, 1969; Apr 13, 1970; Feb 22, 1971*; Apr 29, 1971; Mar 09, 1974*; Feb 11, 1975 (letter from Cunningham's lawyers, Morrison & Foerster); also see Oakland Museum
Hiatt, Mary: Apr 30, 1970; Jul 12, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
High, Dennis: mentioned in letter dated May 10, 1976
Higman, Harry W.: Apr 25, 1953; Jun 08, 1965*; Jun 08, 1965*
Himelfarb, Harvey: Mar 27, 1971
Hoffman, Lee: Jun 09, 1972; Jun 15, 1972*; Dec 19, 1972; Jan 06, 1973*
Hoffman, Michael E.: see Aperture
Holder, Preston: Mar 21, 1966; Apr 12, 1966*; Sep 12, 1966; Sep 13, 1966*; Sep 18, 1966; Oct 11, 1966; Oct 30, 1966*; Jan 23, 1967; Nov 18, 1968; Nov 19, 1968*
Holger, Zelda: Feb 28, 1976
Holt, Rinehart & Winston, Inc.: Sep 26, 1972*; Oct 11, 1972; Oct 16, 1972*; Oct 18, 1972
Holub, Leo: Aug 20, 1969*; Aug 24, 1969; Dec 25, 1973; Jan 1975; Jun 21, 1976
Homestead Productions: Jan 07, 1971
Hooykaas, Else Madelon: Jan 02, 1971; Jun 09, 1971*; Jun 16, 1971; Jan 12, 1972
Hoover, Herbert (the office of Herbert Hoover): May 21, 1935*; Jun 4, 1935; Oct 05, 1935; Oct 09, 1935*; Feb 25, 1936; Feb 28, 1936*; Apr 22, 1936; Apr 29, 1936*; May 06, 1936; May 13, 1936*
Hosoe, Eikoh: Dec 25, 1974
Howell, Thekla and Robinson: [Jan 1966]; Dec 25, 1968; Feb 08, 1969*
Humboldt State College: Jan 21, 1965 (2); Jan 10, 1966; Jan 13, 1966*; Jan 30, 1966*; Feb 22, 1966; Mar 01, 1966*; Jul 01, 1966*; Sep 24, 1966*; Sep 30, 1966; Oct 05, 1966*; Mar 04, 1968*; Apr 05, 1968; Jul 04, 1968*; Feb 06, 1970*
Hume, Portia Bell: Mar 16, 1942; Mar 20, 1942*; May 03, 1942; May 24, 1942*
Hunt Institute for Botanical Documentation: Mar 01, 1974; May 24, 1975*
Huppe: Sep 07, 1973*
Hurd, Mrs.: Aug 09, 1968*
Illinois: University of Illinois: Jan 14, 1965; Feb 01, 1965*; Mar 17, 1965; Mar 26, 1965*; Apr 09, 1965
Imada, Kinji: Jul 07, 1968*; Dec 25, 1971*
Image Circle: Apr 05, 1971*
Indiana University: Oct 31, 1958; Dec 02, 1958
Infinity: Oct 23, 1965*; Nov 07, 1965*; Jan 26, 1966*; Jun 03, 1966*; Jun 20, 1966*; Oct 04, 1966; Oct 14, 1966*; Oct 19, 1966*; May 24, 1967*; also see American Society of Magazine Photographers
Ingalls, David: Feb 22, 1972
Inokuma, Geniciro: Nov 25, 1955
Institute of International Education: Jan 10, 1965*; Mar 26, 1965*; May 03, 1971
International Invitational of Photography: see Volunteer Service Photographers
International Museum of Photography: Feb 10, 1972; May 03, 1972; Jun 16, 1972*; Nov 10, 1974*; also see Eastman: George Eastman House
Iowa: University of Iowa: Nov 14, 1967; Nov 22, 1967*; Nov 24, 1967*; Dec 04, 1967; Jan 04, 1968; Jan 04, 1968; Jan 13, 1968*; Mar 04, 1968*; Oct 29, 1968; Nov 10, 1968*; Nov 16, 1968; Apr 08, 1969; May 26, 1971
Irwin, Clare: undated; Oct 08, 1960*; Nov 04, 1968*; Jan 10, 1969; Feb 25, 1969*; Mar 11, 1969*; Aug 30, 1970*; Sep 11, 1970; Dec 15, 1970; Mar 26, 1971*; Mar 31, 1971; Apr 02, 1971*; Apr 10, 1971; Dec 15, 1971*; May 10, 1972*; May 26, 1972; Jun 08, 1972*; Oct 05, 1972; Oct 19, 1972*; Sep 18, 1973; Nov 30, 1973*; Jan 24, 1974*; Apr 09, 1974; May 23, 1974*; Feb 26, 1976; Mar 06, 1976*; Oct 20, 1976
Irwin? family: Jul 19, 1967 (in German)
Irwin, Melanie: Sep 24, 1971
Iselin, Leni: Aug 25, 1961; Sep 19, 1961; Sep 23, 1961; Oct 17, 1961; Mar 02, 1962; Apr 29, 1962*; May 19, 1962; May 25, 1962*; Jun 12, 1962*; Oct 23, 1962*; Jan 08, 1963*; Mar 29, 1963*; Jul 18, 1963*; Nov 26, 1963*; Jan 03, 1964*; Jun 02, 1964*; Aug 07, 1964*; Nov 17, 1964*; Jun 18, 1967*; Jul 10, 1967*
Istituto Editoriale Domus: Aug 11, 1958; Aug 17, 1958*; Aug 26, 1958
Jackson, Herbet: Oct 16, 1967
Jacobs, Ken: May 21, 1973*
Jameson, Catherine E.: see Marple, Warren
Janis: Sidney Janis Gallery: Feb 23, 1976
Jay, Bill: see Album
Jobert, Muriel: Jan 12, 1960*; Jul 19, 1960; Dec 11, 1960*; Nov 20, 1962; Feb 05, 1964*; Sep 17, 1964*; Dec 12, 1966*; Jan 12, 1967; Feb 04, 1967*; Jun 19, 1967*
Johnson, Catherine: Jan 20, 1968
Johnson, Lyndon B.: Jun 14, 1965 (invitation to reception at the White House)
Johnson, Tom: see College of Marin
Jones, George: Sep 07, 1971; Nov 10, 1971
Jones, Laura: undated
Jourdan, Alda: Jan 15, 1956
Jourdan, Erven: Feb 27, 1976
Junior League of Oakland: Oct 19, 1967
Junior League of San Francisco: Nov 15, 1951; Aug 05, 1965
Ka_____, Kay: [Feb 1973]
Kalamazoo Institute of Arts: Mar 16, 1961; May 22, 1961*; May 24, 1961; Jan 05, 1962
Kalina, Judith: Oct 1972; Mar 14, 1975; May 30, 1975*; Aug 31, 1975
Kalkman, Robert Rodgers: Jan 23, 1973
Kanaga, Consuelo: undated; Mar 05, 1961; Mar 12, 1961*; Jan 06, 1962; May 02, 1968*; May 08, 1968; Feb 25, 1969*; mentioned in letter dated Oct 1972
Kansas: University of Kansas: Mar 05, 1974
Kantor, Jayne: Oct 07, 1974; Oct 13, 1974*; Oct 18, 1974; Jan 15, 1975
Kasler-Holliman, Phyllis: Apr 26, 1967; Mar 30, 1968; Apr 10, 1968*
Kauffman, Eleanor: Oct 21, 1974*
Kauffman, Richard: Mar 08, 1965
Kaufman, Evelyn and Hank: Jun 18, 1976
KCBS-Radio: Apr 14, 1967; also see Writings
Keesling, Mrs. Francis: Sep 08, 1969* (receipt)
Kelly, Dorothea: Jan 04, 1964, (including photograph of a painting in a stairway)
Kelly, Jain: see Witkin Gallery
Kemp, Edward: see Oregon: University of Oregon
Kennedy, Lawton: Feb 16, 1966*
Kent State University Press: Jun 24, 1970
Kewell, Jeanne: Jun 07, 1954; Jun 17, 1954*; Jun 26, 1954; Jul 20, 1954*
Khounta, Penelope: Apr 18, 1973
Kier, Mary Alice: Apr 19, 1971
Kilgore, Don: May 12, 1974; May 25, 1974*; May 25, 1975
Kim-Le, Richard: Apr 01, 1976*
Kingston, Rodger: Dec 22, 1974
Kirkman, Tom: Apr 24, 1972; Jun 24, 1972*; Jun 27, 1972
Kismaric, Carole: see Snyder: Norman Snyder Studios, Inc.
Klemmer, Ruth: Dec 21, 1973 (including 2 photos circa 1916)
Klingenberg, Grace: Jan 07, 1963
Knight, Tom and Katy: Dec 21, 1966* (letter to Guggenheim re Thomas Knight); Jan 21, 1974; Jan 25, 1974*; also see Humboldt State College
Knopf: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc.: Mar 04, 1976; Mar 09, 1976*
Kolbrener, Bob: Dec 02, 1974
Kolisch, Marian Wood (granddaughter of Charles Erskine Scott Wood): Sep 28, 1974
Korty, John: May 21, 1970 (2); Jun 04, 1970*; Jul 20, 1970 (letter from Museum of Modern Art); Jan 24, 1972; Mar 07, 1973; Jan 1974 (3); Feb 09, 1974*; Mar 06, 1976
Koryhut, Wanda: Aug 21, 1957; Aug 30, 1957
Kosmak, Evelyn and George: Jun 19, 1964; Sep 24, 1970
Kouns, John: Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation)
KPIX 5: Apr 07, 1971; Jun 03, 1975 (2); Jun 03, [1975] (2)
KQED: undated; May 12, 1965; Feb 15, 1966; Jun 14, 1971; Aug 07, 1971; Dec 15, 1971*; May 04, 1972; Jun 14, 1972; May 02, 1974; May 01, 1975
Kraft, Jim: undated
Kralka, Ania: Feb 05, 1966; Feb 13, 1967*; May 12, 1967*; Nov 08, 1970*; Jan 1976
Krannert Art Museum: see Illinois: University of Illinois
Krasnow, Peter: May 27, 1976
Krotki, K. J. and Ania: Apr 01, 1961; Dec 25, 1962 (photo Christmas card); Dec 25, 1963 (photo Christmas card); Mar 16, 1970; Jan 18, 1972
Krotta, Krysia: Feb 10, 1959*; Jun 24, 1959; Aug 21, 1959*; Dec 12, 1959*; Nov 25, 1960*; Feb 21, 1961*; Mar 03, 1961*; Mar 09, 1961; Mar 26, 1961*; Apr 13, 1976*
Krupsaw, Warren B.: Apr 18, 1969
Kurtz, Bruce: Apr 18, 1967
KVON (Martha Walker): Sep 27, 1955
Ladies' Home Journal: Aug 24, 1972
Lagrane, Myrtle: Nov 12, 1973
Lamkin, John: Jun 1974; Jun 07, 1974*
Land, Edwin: Mar 09, 1965*
Land, Terre?: Aug 29, [1967]; Sep 07, 1967*; Sep 27, 1967
Lane, William and Saundra: Nov 12, 1968*; Jan 31, 1969*; Feb 27, 1969*; mentioned in letter dated Mar 12, 1969*; Apr 14, 1969*; Apr 18, 1969; Apr 29, 1969*; Jul 30, 1969*; Sep 17, 1969*; Nov 15, 1969; Dec 11, 1969*; Dec 17, 1969; Jan 13, 1970*; Mar 04, 1970*; Aug 24, 1970; Sep 25, 1970*; Oct 20, 1970*; Nov 16, 1970*; Dec 08, 1970; Jul 23, 1971* (2)
Lange, Dorothea: undated; Apr 24, 1958*; Apr 18, 1963*; May 17, 1971 (Dorothea Lange Purchase Award given to Cunningham)
Lanier, Addie Laurie: undated*
Lanier, Eiko: Feb 10, 1963*; Feb 22, 1964*; also see Photographs
Lanier, Ruth Asawa: see Asawa, Ruth
La Paz Pottery: Jun 13, 1973*
Larson, Jerry: see Mount Angel Abbey Library
Laszlo, Ernie: see Writings
Latent Image (Gallery): Mar 19, 1971
Laub, Randolph (Ohio Silver [gallery]): May 14, 1973*; Jun 28, 1973; Jul 24, 1973*
Laughlin, Clarence John: Jan 06, 1952
Laurel, Stan: mentioned in letter dated Feb 22, 1976
Lavenson, Alma: Aug 19, 1953*; Jun 25, 1954*; Dec 07, 1959*; Apr 12, [1968]; Jul 31, 1968*
Lee, Alan W. S.: Jan 11, 1913 (including 14 photographs of China); Apr 17, 1916; Oct 26, 1917; Jan 05, 1918; Mar 1918; Aug 21, 1918 (including 8 photographs of Japanese ceramics); Jan 07, 1919; May 09, 1919; Jun 11, 1919; Jan 14, [1920]; Mar 23, 1920; Apr 14, 1920; May 13, 1920; Jul 17, 1920; Sep 13, 1920; Oct 17, 1920; Dec 01, 1920; Feb 03, 1921; Feb 13, 1921; May 29, 1921; Sep 20, 1921 (including a photograph of the Thames River and Tower Bridge, 4 of Peking, one of a Nagasaki fountain, and one of Poyang Lake); Nov 25, 1921; Jan 09, 1922; Feb 09, 1922; Apr 05, 1922; Aug 24, 1922; Nov 28, 1922; Jan 19, 1923; Aug 31, 1923; Feb 09, 1924; Aug 13, 1924; Mar 23, 1926; Dec 01, 1926; Jan 28, 1927; Jun 02, 1927; Aug 26, 1932; Feb 22, 1934; Oct 18, 1934; Jan 04, 1937 (including 3 photographs of Diplomatic Corps ceremony); Jul 12, 1938; Aug 11, 1939; Aug 31, 1939; Jan 19, 1940
Lee, Hannah Simms: Jan 19, 1957; Feb 12, 1957*; Jun 11, 1965*; Mar 03, 1971*; Mar 13, 1971*
Leefe, Miriam: May 31, 1963*; [Jun 1963]; Aug 07, 1963*; Sep 27, 1963*; Nov 23, 1963*
Lemkin, Mari: Aug 02, 1962; Aug 06, 1962*
Lentz, Bernard: Mar 13, 1958; Nov 23, 1958; Jan 02, 1960; Feb 07, 1960
Leonard, Gini Dodge: Nov 12, 1971; also see undated letter from Cunningham to the Guggenheim Foundation
Leonard, Joanne: Jun 16, 1974
Leone, Anna: Feb 07, 1969*
Leslie, Caird: May 05, 1956*; Dec 10, 1961
Levi Strauss and Company: mentioned in letters dated Sep 20, 1972 and Sep 29, 1972*
Lewis, Carol: Sep 17, 1975
Library of Congress: mentioned in [undated] letter from Cunningham to unidentified correspondent; Jul 14, 1949; Nov 16, 1949; Sep 05, 1962; Dec 03, 1962; Mar 18, 1963; Mar 27, 1963*; May 07, 1963; May 20, 1963*; Jul 08, 1963*; Jul 17, 1963; Jul 30, 1963; Nov 14, 1963; Nov 20, 1963*; Dec 30, 1963*; Feb 18, 1964; Mar 19, 1964*; Mar 26, 1964; Apr 07, 1964*; Apr 15, 1964; Apr 24, 1964*; Jun 04, 1964; Oct 08, 1964
Life: Dec 29, 1959*; Sep 19, 1969*; Oct 02, 1969; Oct 27, 1969; Mar 13, 1970 (2); May 06, 1970; Jan 14, 1972*; Aug 31, 1972; Oct 03, 1972; Oct 09, 1972*; Nov 03, 1972*; Nov 06, 1972*; Dec 29, 1972*; Jan 05, 1973; Jan 26, 1973
LIMELIGHT (exhibitions): Sep 17, 1954; Oct 06, 1954*; Oct 21, 1954*; Jan 10, 1955; Jan 21, 1955*; Mar 08, 1955; Apr 01, 1955*; Apr 25, 1955; Sep 14, 1955; Oct 03, 1955*; Nov 10, 1955*; Feb 24, 1956; Mar 25, 1956*
Linenthal, Alice Adams: Jul 23, 1966
Liston, Mrs. J. Glen: see Western Association of Art Museums
Littlejohn, David: Jun 05, 1970*
Locks, Norman: see Adams: Ansel Adams Gallery
Logan: Reva and David Logan Foundation: Feb 17, 1970; Apr 13, 1970*; Sep 13, 1971*; Nov 16, 1971*; Aug 03, 1973; Mar 25, 1974; Jun 05, 1975
London Times: Dec 30, 1963
Look: Dec 05, 1969; Dec 09, 1969*; Dec 24, 1969*; Jan 09, 1970; May 12, 1970*; May 25, 1970; Mar 13, 1971*; Mar 20, 1971*; Feb 1973; Mar 28, 1973*
Lovatt?, Bill: Jan 06, 1961*
Loveless family: Mar 09, 1971*
Ludington, Wright: Feb 13, 1953
Lushington, Beatrice: Jul 19, 1976
Luther, Dr. R. and Ida: Sep 28, 1923 (in German); Aug 01, 1927 (in German)
Lynch: Douglas Lynch Associates Graphic Design: Sep 20, [1966]
Lyons, Nathan: Nov 20, 1963; Jun 29, 1967*
MacCormack, Robert: Dec 04, 1956*
MacDonald, Dorothy and Helen (Helen MacDonald Guthrie): undated; Mar 09, 1961; Aug 28, 1962 (letter from Helen Dickinson-Chetham); Jun 30, 1965*; Aug 31, 1965*; Jan 24, 1966*; Jul 02, 1966*; Sep 01, 1966*; Jan 03, 1967*; May 29, 1967*; Jul 31, 1967*; Aug 02, 1967; Aug 14, 1967*; Oct 29, 1967*; [Jan 1968]*; Jan 01, 1968 (letter from Joan and Bruce Haynes); Mar 20, 1968*; Mar 27, 1968; Jun 10, 1968*; Jul 05, 1968*; Jul 19, 1968*; Apr 15, 1969*; Apr 20, 1970*; Apr 30, 1970; [Jul 1970]; Jul 19, 1970*; Nov 18, 1970*; [Nov 21, 1970]; Jan 16, 1971*; Jan 30, 1971*; Jul 26, 1971*; Oct 07, 1972*; [Dec 25, 1973]; Feb 14, 1974; [Feb 14, 1974]; Feb 20, 1974*; Mar 26, 1974*; May 16, 1974; Jun 24, 1974 (letter to Gryffyd Partridge); Oct 03, 1974*; Nov 21, 1974*; Dec 28, 1974*; Jun 25, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Macfadden Publications, Inc.: Jul 22, 1942
MacGalliard, Wally: Jun 03, 1972; Jun 07, 1972*
MacKay, Alastair: Jun 05, 1972*; Jul 30, 1973*; Aug 11, 1973; Aug 27, 1973*
Mackland, Ray: Feb 10, 1960*
Macmillan Company: Jun 23, 1936; Aug 08, 1939; Aug 31, 1939*
Maddox, Miss (of Atrium): Jun 01, 1966*
Madison Art Center: May 25, 1973; Jun 28, 1973; Jan 15, 1974; May 07, 1974*
Maimone, Paul: Jul 10, 1974; Nov 08, 1974*
Malanga, Gerard: Mar 21, 1973
Malarkey, Mr.: Jul 08, 1965*
Malcolm, Ida Parton: Jul 23, 1967*
Mandel, Mike: Aug 22, 1975 (including 3 postcards designed by Mandel and a baseball card picturing Cunningham holding a ball and glove); Nov 13, 1975
Mann, Margery: undated (3); Jan 08, 1966; Oct 04, 1966 (letter to Infinity including a typescript "Imogen Cunningham" by Mann); Sep 25, 1967 (letter to Don Ellegood); Aug 09, 1968*; Oct 10, 1968 (letter from Ellegood); Oct 14, 1968*; mentioned in letter dated Apr 29, 1969; Aug 10, 1969; Apr 1970; May 18, 1970 (letter from Washington Press); Feb 08, 1971*; Mar 03, 1971*; Nov 16, 1972; Mar 30, 1973*; Sep 08, 1973*; Feb 06, 1974*; Apr 24, 1974; Aug 21, 1974 (letter from Cunningham's lawyers, Morrison, Foerster, Holloway, Clinton & Clark); Aug 27, 1974 (2); also see Writings
Manning, Harvey: see Washington: University of Washington, Seattle
Manself Press: Oct 26, 1974
Marcus, Lynn: undated
Maring: Dennis E. Maring & Co.: Nov 13, 1975
Marks, Milton (State Senator, Wash.): Nov 24, 1970; Nov 26, 1970*
Marple, Warren, Lorna, and Elliot: Jun 25, 1965; August 1966*; Apr 15, 1974 (2); May 18, 1974; May 21, 1974*; Dec 21, 1974
Martinez, Caroline, Zoura, and Al: Apr 24, 1974; Feb 25, 1975*; Jun 29, 1976
Masclet, Daniel: [Dec 1960] (in French); Dec 06, 1960*; Nov 16, 1961; Jun 13, 1963*
Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Jan 10, 1968; Jan 29, 1968; Feb 25, 1968; Mar 25, 1968; Apr 11, 1968; May 20, 1968; Jun 05, 1969; May 25, 1970; also see White, Minor
Massar, Phyllis: undated (2); Dec 20, 1963; Oct 01, 1969; Oct 08, 1969*; Apr 11, 1970; Aug 08, 1970; Aug 14, 1970*; Sep 03, 1970; Sep 10, 1970*; Sep 14, 1970; Sep 15, 1970*; Oct 01, 1970; Oct 05, 1970*; Oct 17, 1970; Nov 08, 1970; Nov 12, 1970*; Dec 11, 1970; Feb 22, 1971*; Feb 28, 1971; Mar 05, 1971; Mar 12, 1971; Jan 05, 1973; Jan 08, 1973*; Mar 07, 1973; Mar 19, 1973*; Mar 29, 1973; Apr 09, 1973; Apr 25, 1973; Mar 27, 1974*; Jun 23, 1974; Jul 23, 1974; Dec 15, 1974
Mathias, Mr.: Dec 12, 1967*
Mattison, Ethel and Jack: Nov 09, 1947; Dec 25, 1966; Jan 24, 1967*; Oct 12, 1968*
Maugham, W. Somerset: mentioned in letter dated Jun 10, 1936
Mayer, Grace M.: see Museum of Modern Art
Mayer, Helene: see Falkner von Sonnenburg, Helene
Mayer, Ida: Jan 03, 1955 (in German)
Mayes, Elaine: Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation)
Mazzeo family: Dec 31, 1959*
McBride, Mary Margaret: Jan 10, 1961; May 06, 1969; Oct 24, 1970*
McCabe, Darlene: Jan 26, 1976
McCann-Erickson, Inc.: Dec 22, 1970; Dec 30, 1970*; Feb 04, 1971*; Feb 12, 1971*; Mar 05, 1971
McCarthy: Oct 14, 1959*
McCarthy, Jane: Nov 07, 1970
McClatchy, Phebe: Nov 26, 1951
McDougal, Littell & Company: Feb 11, 1970
McEwan, Mary: undated (4); Oct 11, 1954*; Nov 18, 1954*; Dec 26, 1954*; Jan 02, 1955; Jan 14, 1955*; Feb 02, 1955; Feb 25, 1955*; Feb 28, 1955*; Mar 14, 1955*; Mar 27, 1955; Apr 20, 1955; May 11, 1955; May 29, 1955*; Jun 23, 1955; Jul 14, 1955*; Aug 03, 1955; Aug 30, 1955; Sep 22, 1955; Oct 03, 1955*; Oct 12, 1955; Oct 21, 1955 (2); Nov 22, 1955; Dec 11, 1955*; Jan 06, 1956; Jan 16, 1956*; Jan 10, 1956*; Apr 22, 1956 (married to Rex Dadd); Jun 06, 1958; Jun 27, 1958*; Dec 1958; Mar 16, 1959; May 04, 1959; Sep 27, 1959*; Jan 01, 1960*; Feb 13, 1960*; Nov 29, 1960*; Feb 13, 1961; Feb 26, 1961*; May 16, 1961*
McGraw, Dick: Dec 25, 1966; Jun 15, 1967*; Mar 08, 1968*
McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc.: Mar 29, 1961
McHugh, Vincent: Mar 11, 1970; May 15, 1970; May 21, 1970*
McIntosh, Jenny: Dec 19, 1947
McKee, Tasheira & Wahrhaftig: May 11, 1939 (divorce decree)
McLeod, James: Jun 11, 1970 (letter from Beatrice Roethke); Jul 05, 1970*; Jul 11, 1970*
McLuhan, Teri: see Outerbridge & Dienstfrey
McMinn, Helen: Jan 28, 1972
Mees, Kenneth: Jul 19, 1957*; Jul 26, 1957; Feb 05, 1958*; Jun 01, 1958*; Aug 26, 1958*
Melchert, Ralph (Ramel): Sep 19, 1973
Meltzer, Milton: Jan 27, 1976
Menapace, John: Mar 06, 1969; May 31, 1970*; Jun 10, 1970; Jun 18, 1970*
Mendocino Art Center: Feb 15, 1971; Feb 22, 1971*
Mendocino Historical Research, Inc.: Mar 04, 1976
Menninger, Edwin: undated
Merrill, Forrest: Oct 21, 1974*
Mesaros, Ron: Oct 02, 1970; Oct 11, 1970*
Metcalf: Addison M. Metcalf Collection of Gertrude Steiniana: Mar 23, 1955; Sep 22, 1955*; Sep 26, 1955; Oct 11, 1955
Metropolitan Museum of Art: Jul 12, 1969*; Jul 21, 1969; Aug 11, 1969*; Aug 13, 1969; Aug 16, 1969*; Dec 16, 1969; Dec 21, 1969*; Jan 14, 1970; Feb 22, 1970*; Apr 30, 1970; May 07, 1970*; May 14, 1970; May 31, 1970*; Jun 16, 1970; Nov 30, 1970; Mar 11, 1971; Mar 17, 1971; Mar 22, 1971*; Apr 14, 1971; Feb 20, 1973; Mar 02, 1973*; Mar 08, 1973; Mar 17, 1973* (2); May 15, 1973*; May 31, 1973; Jul 17, 1973
Metzker, Ray: Sep 14, 1960; Dec 06, 1960*; Feb 12, 1962; Apr 27, 1962*
Miles, Josephine: Apr 02, 1973
Miller, Barbara J.: undated
Mills College: Mar 19, 1954; May 14, 1954; May 24, 1954; Jan 27, 1956; Feb 27, 1956*; Apr 11, 1956; Apr 14, 1956*; May 29, 1958; Feb 22, 1965; Apr 08, 1970*; Sep 06, 1973; Sep 08, 1973*; Feb 11, 1975; Feb 25, 1975; Apr 04, 1975*; May 13, 1975*
Minard, F.: Dec 29, 1966
Mind's Eye (gallery): Oct 25, 1973
Minneapolis Institute of Arts: Mar 29, 1957
Mocy?, Robert: Apr 04, 1965
Model, Lisette: May 21, 1970; Jun 11, 1971
Modern Photography: Dec 12, 1950 (typescript of "A Passion for the Medium" by Christina); Feb 27, 1951; Aug 11, 1953; Jul 06, 1954*; Apr 14, 1955; Jan 13, 1956*; Aug 23, 1957*; Feb 01, 1968; Aug 08, 1968; Apr 18, 1972
Moholy-Nagy, L.: Jan 04, 1941
Monk, Heidi: Apr 02, 1969; Apr 14, 1970
Monterey Peninsula College: Jan 21, 1970; Jan 26, 1970*; Jan 27, 1970; Mar 03, 1970; Mar 04, 1970; Mar 11, 1970*; Apr 15, 1970*
Moon, Orrin C.: see Mendocino Art Center
Moore, Richard: May 22, 1975
Morais, Ka: Feb 10, 1976
Morais, Ken: mentioned in letter dated May 10, 1976
Morgan, Barbara and Willard: Jan 09, 1967; Apr 10, 1968*; Dec 26, 1969*; Nov 29, 1970; Dec 03, 1970*
Morgan, Edith: Oct 14, 1953; Jan 03, 1955*; Jun 30, 1957*
Morgan Guaranty Trust Co.: Aug 16, 1969*
Morley, S. Griswold: Oct 09, 1961; Jul 14, [1962]; Jul 08, 1968*; Aug 09, 1968*; also see Printed Material
Morris, Mark: Apr 09, 1974
Morrison, Foerster, Holloway, Clinton & Clark: Aug 21, 1974 (letter to Marjorie Mann); Aug 21, 1974 (letter to Gryffyd Partridge); Sep 11, 1974; Feb 11, 1975 (letter to Theresa Heyman); Feb 18, 1975 (letter to Gryffyd Partridge and Adrian Wilson); Feb 27, 1975; Mar 17, 1975
Morros, Boris: see Notes for Jane Foster's excerpts from My Ten Years as a Counterspy by Morros, 1959
Mount Angel Abbey Library: Apr 03, 1970; Aug 30, 1971; Sep 06, 1971*; Sep 24, 1971*; Oct 07, 1971; Oct 17, 1971*; Nov 07, 1971*; Nov 08, 1971; Nov 26, 1971; Dec 02, 1971*; Dec 17, 1971; Jan 07, 1972*; Feb 14, 1972; Mar 16, 1974*; also see Photographs
Mozesson, Phiz: mentioned in letter dated Dec 16, 1970*
Mozley, Anita: Apr 08, 1973*; Jun 09, 1973; Jun 15, 1973*
Ms.: Nov 25, 1974; Apr 26, 1975*
Muffley, Dick: Jul 06, 1968*; May 04, 1973 (including a photograph of himself, 2 of his house, and 4 of an atom smasher); May 19, 1973*; May 17, 1974*; May 19, 1974 (including 3 vacation photographs and a photograph of Cliff Freehe)
Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute: Jan 09, 1957; Feb 16, 1957*; Feb 19, 1957*; Feb 21, 1957; Feb 28, 1957
Museum of Fine Arts, Springfield, Mass.: Jun 03, [1974]; Aug 13, 1974; Aug 16, 1974*
Museum of Modern Art: undated; Apr 02, 1937; Sep 17, 1941; Sep 25, 1941*; Oct 22, 1946; Oct 28, 1946; Jan 01, 1960*; Mar 01, 1960; Mar 14, 1960; Apr 08, 1960; Apr 12, 1960; Jun 02, 1960; Nov 03, 1960; Dec 30, 1960; Jan 10, 1961*; Jan 16, 1961; Feb 01, 1961*; Feb 03, 1961; Feb 07, 1961*; May 19, 1961; Apr 04, 1962; May 29, 1962; May 30, 1962; Mar 26, 1963; Apr 05, 1963*; May 03, 1963; May 20, 1963; May 30, 1963*; Jun 04, 1963; Jun 16, 1963*; Jul 02, 1963; Jul 04, 1963*; Jul 08, 1963*; Jul 22, 1963; Aug 07, 1963*; Aug 12, 1963; Oct 16, 1963*; Oct 28, 1963; Oct 31, 1963; Nov 08, 1963*; Dec 12, 1963; Jan 25, 1964*; Jan 29, 1964; Apr 13, 1964; Apr 21, 1964; Jun 01, 1964; Jun 08, 1964; Sep 21, 1964*; Sep 29, 1964; Jan 02, 1965*; Jan 06, 1965; Jul 15, 1965 (2); Jul 28, 1965* (2); Sep 30, 1965; Oct 12, 1965*; Oct 20, 1965; Nov 14, 1965; Jul 28, 1966*; Jul 31, 1966; Aug 11, 1966; Sep 01, 1966*; Sep 06, 1966; Nov 09, 1966*; Dec 01, 1966; Dec 07, 1966; Jan 25, 1967 (2); Apr 03, 1967; Apr 07, 1967*; Apr 10, 1967*; May 23, 1967; Jun 17, 1967; Dec 09, 1967; Feb 13, 1968; May 15, 1968; Jun 13, 1968; Jul 11, 1968; Sep 12, 1968*; Oct 09, 1968; Oct 21, 1968; May 10, 1969; Jul 14, 1969*; Sep 05, 1969; Sep 08, 1969; Apr 09, 1970; Apr 21, 1970; Jul 20, 1970 (letter to John Korty); Nov 18, 1970; Mar 08, 1971; Aug 04, 1971*; Sep 07, 1971*; Feb 16, 1972; Apr 10, 1973*; Dec 18, 1974; Dec 24, 1974*; Jun 09, 1975; also see Steichen, Edward
Myers, Evelyn: Jan 29, 1958*
Nathan, Joan: Jul 07, 1969*
National Council on the Aging, Inc.: Jan 23, 1973 (including booklet "Older Americans and the Arts: A Human Equation")
National Institute of Arts and Letters: Jan 05, 1961*
National Organization for Women: Jun 18, 1974
NBC: see TONIGHT SHOW
Nebraska: University of Nebraska: Nov 03, 1965; Nov 20, 1965*; Mar 17, 1966; Apr 04, 1966*; Apr 25, 1966; Jun 02, 1966*; Jun 14, 1966; Jul 19, 1966; Jul 25, 1966*; Jul 28, 1966; Aug 26, 1966*; Sep 06, 1966; Sep 12, 1966*; Nov 01, 1966; Nov 10, 1966*; Nov 16, 1966; Dec 21, 1966*; Mar 17, 1967*; Mar 23, 1967
Neevel, Paul: see Writings
Nesbit, Norman: Mar 30, 1969*
Neumann, J. B.: see New Art Circle
Neumeyer, Fred (Alfred): Apr 15, 1970
New American Library: Jul 08, 1966*; Jul 10, 1967; Jul 19, 1967*
New Art Circle (J. B. Neumann, Dir.): Oct 22, 1937